TOFIK MOHAMMED

EMAIL: tofik.a.moh1999@gmail.com **WEBSITE:** http://tofweb.services **PHONE:** 6473541889 **LOCATION:** Toronto, ON **GITHUB:** https://github.com/tofi-124

SUMMARY

I am a professional Web developer, mastering various platforms and experience with different language such as HTML and Javascript; and CSS and frameworks like React, Node as well as experience in SQL and PSQL. Also dedicated programmer with a curious mind and strong problem-solving abilities with proven collaboration, communication, and interpersonal skills.

EDUCATION

Lighthouse Labs, Diploma in Full-Stack Web Development	2021 - 2022
BSC Computer Security (Partial Completion)	2020 - 2021

EMPLOYMENT

CIBC, Fraud and Dispute Specialist

NPower Digital Customer Care

June 2019 - May 2020

2019 - 2019

- Took full responsibility for client calls, responding to them in a warm, courteous, and professional manner and ensuring prompt resolution of identified concerns while managing risk and offering an amazing client experience.
- Created dispute cases and fraud reports for CIBC Visa and Mastercard cardholders in order to initiate charge-backs.
- Used my in-depth fraud knowledge and problem-solving skills to identify and act on potential fraud transactions.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES: HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, Java, C++

LIBRARIES/FRAMEWORK: REACT, RUBY, NODE EXPRESS, AJAX, PSQL, Next Js, Jquery, Commerce JS

`

PROJECTS

Scheduler

Students can connect with mentors in real-time through this React-based web app and schedule meetings.

Tech Stack: Axios, React, Cypress, Classnames, React-dom, Normalize.css

Tweeter Project

Tweeter is a simple, single-page web clone of twitter built using AJAX.

Tech Stack: Express, jQuery, Node

Resource Wall Project

Resource-Wall is a full stack web application built with Node and Express that allows users to save resources, as well as register and login. Any user can rate or comment on a resource, and other users can see the average rating as well as other users' comments.

Tech Stack: Express, Node.JS

AWARDS

Excel Rate Award, Cibc

2020

The Excelerate quarterly award is given to those that have maintained a balanced performance for the duration of the quarter.